When they were at the intersection Enhörnaleden/Robert Anberg's road, the killer appeared on an electric bike, stopped and shot dead the 41-year-old.
Now, 13 \ Hmen, one of whom, are charged with murder, two as fellow or assistants, and others for gross protection of criminals and failure to reveal murder.
The motif is believed to revenge a death shoot that took place the day before when George Shaya was shot dead, the event was part of the ongoing gang conflict between different phalanges in Södertälje.
The prosecutor's theory is that the murder of the 41-year-old was a so-called mistake.
The shooting was the \ hfjärde shooting in Södertälje in a week.
The murder has been expected despite very high police presence in the area as a result of previous shootings in Södertälje and is founded in an infected conflict between two criminal groups in Södertälje.
After the murder of their friend the day, before probably performed by the Ronna side, the gang is revenge and bloodthirsty.
Despite the massive police presence in Södertälje at the moment, they go out and spin for enemies.
The so -called Saltskog Falangen has a specific target they are looking for this evening.
T who is linked to Ronna Falangen, T is appearance like the death victim and was near the murder scene but that the shooter was wrong.
Surveillance films show that the intended target T and two other people were at the Ron-A school on Robert Anberg's road 24 in Södertälje between 19:28 and 19:40 in the evening.
Police were alerted at 19.41 to the district \ Hronna \ Hi \ Hsödertälje after several people must have called in after hearing a gunfire.
The shooter leaves the crime scene on an electric bike in the direction of Lina in Södertälje.
On October 2, 20, 22, an unlocked garage you are searching on the ceramic road in Lina in Södertälje.
You will find an electric bike and a protective vest as well as a bag containing weapons, magazines and garments.
Some people leave the room by car while the shooting takes place.
L2 and Guldish are stopped in a car 21:39 on the murder night while Guldish mobile phone shows that he is on the way to Tumba, Botkyrka municipality in the car where those who left Lina at the time of the murder are in.
An attempt to give, among other things, Guldish an alibi at the murder according to the prosecutor.
The Glock 22 found in the room is found to be the murder weapon.
It has been used at least for two previous shootings in Södertälje.
First a shooting against Rösberga preschool center in Södertälje in December 2013. And also in September 2014 when five bullet holes were found in a building and 14 empty sleeves were found at Robert Anberg's road in Ronna, Södertälje when people on a moped shoot.
Both murdered G and "Guldish" were linked to a serious weapons crime on July 27, 2022 in Lina.
At the scene, where a police officer has been spoken of a conversation about gunfire, cartridge sleeves and bullets were found, that the cartridge sleeves are fired in the murder weapon found in the garage on the ceramic road and the cartridges rehearsed/handled in the said weapon and that DNA from Guldish was detected on a water bottle and a beverage can
And DNA from George has been detected on a cigarette fimp.
The autopsy protocols regarding the victim show that he suffered 19 gunshot injuries as a result of ball weapons and that he died as a result of extensive damage to the skull and the brain.
One of the shots that hit the face was judged to be at least one close shot, a execution, fired in the Glock gun found on October 2.
As well as most noted gunshot injuries in the arms, back and chest.
No visible damage was noted on the lower body.
According to several witnesses who also photographed, the shooter fled on an electric bike in the direction of Lina.
The previously mentioned garage on the ceramic road is located there and it takes about 2 minutes and 52 seconds to get from the murder scene to the garage on electric bike.
Maikel, 23, is charged with murder or assisting in murder or gross protection of criminal.
Franki and Maikel, both of them are charged with being fellow or assistants at the murder of the 41-year-old on October 1.
The two must take care of the Goldish mobile phone before the shooting and then before, during and after the crime brought the phone by car from Södertälje to, among other things.
Alby and Tumba since the day after returned the phone.
The measures have been intended to counteract the fact that it is discovered that Guldish committed the crime and/or that he is held responsible.
L2, 26 years, is charged with serious weapons offenses, nutritional laundering, gross protection of criminal, failure to reveal murder and for stamping for murder.
Since L2 is the one who is charged with contacting and talking to the Kurdish fox from the Foxtrot network about killing and ordering murder on at least three main characters within rival Ronna Falangen.
Several other men linked to Saltskogs Falangen are charged with various crimes, serious weapons offenses, gross protection of criminal and failure to reveal murder.